
Info
	Calendar
		-change from "Google Calender" to "Team Calendar"✓

Home	
	-Update Photos
	-New Sponsor collage (use T Shirt back)
	-update game✓

FIRST
	Move Challenges to FIRST page, add Recycle Rush✓, remove Challenges page
	Game animations

Media
	Phhotos
		rename Photo Media to Team Photos✓
		update photos incorporate Flickr
	Videos
		Rename video Media to Team Videos✓
			most recent videos first, rank by importance

Robots	
	Remove "The Robots" link from left
	
		